I'm not going to die, I'm not going to die
Please, everyone, I beg
you, won't you help me?
NAKAM!
NAKAM has always had a weakness for
your basic, conventional beauty.
But I prefer the cute, devilish type.
I guarantee you, no well-bred
young lady is gonna blow my mind.
So cute!
I just can't!
Suki! Are you okay?
Hang in there, man! My
brain! My brain! Crap!
Well, it's gonna be okay,
Because the only thing this
man goes for are slightly
depressed girls who suddenly
give you an embarrassed,
unexpected smile.
She can't possibly be all
those types wrapped up in one,
even if she is a real-life princess.
And now, our honored hero
will make an appearance.
Come on, hero, give us a smile.
Justice is on our side!
Amazing head maid! Thank you,
the uniforms you procured
and your instructions
on how to behave made everything so easy!
How did things end up like this?
And why do I have to get up
on stage like a pop idol?
This skirt is way too short!
It feels so dangerous and drafty!
The thought that my that which must not be
seen might be seen is
about to drive me insane!
If I get too cold it might upset my tummy!
I can't believe that I'm missing
the stupid tides I usually wear!
Plus, I can't shake this
intense feeling of shame!
I'd rather be naked!
I can't do this! I've gotta change!
Princess, I think it might be
time to begin the next phase.
And what phase is that?
We need an armed uprising.
No, violence is uncivilized.
I've asked our dear citizens
to help us, so I won't do that.
I simply can't have them getting hurt.
At most, we'll use starvation tactics.
I'll make them capitulate
without any bloodshed.
Yes, understood.
As you will it, your highness.
Hold on.
It's been a year since you
started serving me, right?
There are only two reasons
I've come this far.
The hero and the plan you
thought up. Thank you.
If you'll excuse me.
Yes, I'll leave it to you.
That is so much better!
This is how it should be!
The rebellion isn't going away, is it?
Which means I'm gonna have to keep wearing
this uniform in front of
huge crowds of people!
Okay, I'll run away!
Sorry Eggie!
I'm just not ready to be out here trying
to tempt people with my bare legs!
It's a hero!
The hero has showed herself!
This hero!
Just show us the way,
we'll follow you anywhere!
Guess I'll look for the tiara
the handmaid took first.
No idea where I should
start looking, though.
Is someone there?
Eh?
Thank you!
When the headmaid caught me, I had
no idea what I was going to do.
For a sec, I thought you were
doing this recreationally.
That'll be a hard no.
Why don't you come back with me for now?
I know Jinguji is worried about you, too.
You better not follow me!
I was just thinking about
how he hasn't come to get me.
Not very gallant, but I
know what he's thinking.
Why don't you go travel
with the princess, then?
Oh, that's so Jinguuji.
I did not need to do that!
Is someone there?
Oh, that's not good.
Sorry, Muriya!
Oh, Kate!
Please, don't leave me behind!
This sucks.
I'm completely helpless.
Oh, everything's going wrong! Breathe.
I've made it through everything that's
happened to me in this
world one way or another.
No, I can't even delude myself that far.
Jinguji's the one that helped
me survive all this chaos.
boss.
I'm no hero.
Wow, you know, Tachibana, it's
amazing that Jinguji puts up with you
considering how you are.
Are you sure he doesn't think
of you as a pain in the butt?
What am
I even doing here?
Oh, honored hero. Are you well?
Does the fragrance of the tea
not suit Your tastes oh no it's
not that headmaid can I ask you
am I really being useful here?
It seems you might be a
little tired honored hero!
Leave everything to me I'll take care of
it what is that and where is it gonna go?
How is it?
It's the best!
Hey, what is this slippery stuff?
Slime.
The beauty secret of the royal family.
Beauty is a strange thing, isn't it?
It has the power to
seduce or guide someone.
Thanks to your beauty, honored hero,
her highness's wishes, and granted so?
Yes, I Think you're
being quite helpful, huh?
Wow, thanks for saying so!
You don't know how Much
I needed to hear that!
Lots of stuff has happened
since I came here to this World,
but Chinkoji is the one
who's dealt with all of it.
I just wish he Understood how often
I feel like he doesn't need me.
I mean, I know he's super Tired.
Actually, I keep thinking that it's
possible he could die because of me.
I don't understand!
How did things end up like this?
I've heard tell that your body was
bestowed upon you by the goddess
And you continue to face
danger due to your beauty.
Your body's too frail to defend
itself, which makes me think
The goddess is the true
cause of everything.
Is she not?
So it wasn't my fault?
This is all the goddesses bad?
Honored hero, I can understand
what you're going through.
It may be presumptuous of me.
But if you'll allow me, I would
very much like to help Grant here.
Yep, the best snack to pair
with a drink has to be...
Ta-da! Squid!
It's time to look after
my little ones on the
ground while enjoying
a yummy evening drink.
What's this?
Have I finally started
interfering directly then?
You're jealous, aren't you?
Even though it's you who truly
possesses the status of hero,
Jinguji keeps blatantly ignoring that?
and now you find yourself
envying him, don't you?
Yeah.
Let's try keeping our
distance from him for a while
and you will gain power.
I will teach you how to do so.
Yeah.
And then we'll be able to show everyone
what an outstanding human you truly are.
Yeah.
I had a dream about when I was little.
My vision was blurred with tears,
so I'm guessing it might
not have been a good dream.
I feel like elementary school was when
there was the most irrational violence.
Getting picked on sucks.
It hurts, it's humiliating,
it's frustrating.
Bullies know exactly how to make a
person feel as small as possible.
And I just wished for someone, anyone.
I wanted someone to beat
those guys up for me.
This dude's scary. Let's go.
Hey you okay?
Oh now I get it!
This is my memory of the first
time I ever met Jinguuji.
Hey thanks man! Sure thing!
If somebody's in trouble
it's only right to help!
We were in the same class but he always
kept to himself I didn't understand him.
That was so cool!
Were you doing judo?
You're super strong!
Oh wow!
I guess I'd never thought about it.
But ever since I first met him for real.
I idolized him or maybe was I
jealous of him somehow I feel like I.
I'm a terrible guy.
Oh no did I fall asleep?
Yes part way through!
Ah really I'm sorry about that.
But physically and mentally
I feel so much better!
Thanks for the back rub head maid.
No not at all!
I'm glad to know I've been of use to you!
You must be tired!
I think it's Best if you take
today off and get some sleep!
Great!
Sounds like a plan!
Good night then!
Good night to you, too.
Have an even more
pleasant dream this time.
Ah, that's amazing.
I'm here to report that the
person you requested has arrived.
Is it true?
Let him through, then.
Let him through.
He requested someone.
Um, excuse the intrusion.
So, hey, what do you say?
Is it okay if I come in or
do I just hang out here?
Hey, it's Jinguuji!
I'm so glad there's someone I know here!
Oh, it's you.
Hello there, Schwartz.
It's been a while, huh?
Yes, it really has.
But wait, where's Tachibana?
Currently with the princess.
What?
Princess?
There's a princess?
Whoa, I want to meet her!
Think I can?
Actually, I'm about to have an audience
with the king of the entire land,
if you could wrap your head around that.
I barely can myself.
I am super nervous. So weird,
right? For real, though.
Oh, hold on.
Are you sort of waiting for
an audience, too, Jinko-Chi?
Stay calm, Schwarz. Huh?
This is the king of this land.
Ah, indeed.
What an energetic youth!
Just a touch older than
my daughter, I'd guess.
I'm so sorry.
Can I please take that entrance again?
You must do as you wish, of course.
It's a great honor to
meet you, Your Majesty!
As for me, my name is
Schwarz von Liechtensteherr!
Your Majesty, we have given great offense.
No, not at all. Raise your heads.
I know you've suffered many
hardships, so I thank you for coming.
To get straight to the
point, Lord Schwarz.
Due to a rebellion led by
my beloved daughter Iggy,
I'm afraid this kingdom is
currently in a very perilous state.
Her speeches convinced villagers and
castle townsfolk alike to join her,
and they're now a great military force.
Perhaps due to lack of leadership.
A portion of them are now said to be
rioting in an uprising even as we speak.
However, for many years we've been in a
stalemate with the country across the sea.
As such, we have no choice but to continue
focusing our military might there.
That's why we lack the manpower
for a suppression force.
We don't want to use our last
resort if at all possible.
Last resort?
So, what do you say?
Are you willing to save
our kingdom, Lord Schwartz?
Alright, yeah! Let's do it!
Excuse us for a moment. Oh, sure.
Schwarz,
how many times have I told you to stop
answering questions without thinking?
There's a good chance
they'll use your status as
hero to get you caught up
in some nefarious plot.
But Master, I...
If there's rioting, then that means the
village and the people are in danger.
I can think about where I
stand in this later, okay?
If there are people in
trouble, I want to save them.
If my strength can be of any use at all,
then that'll have to be enough
for me right now, alright?
You really care that much?
Wow!
Master, did you seriously
make dinner tonight?
Master, I will overcome this hurdle.
This wall.
One day, Master, I'd like
to visit your homeland.
Master!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Can it be true that Shvarts has actually
grown enough to say something like this?
Master, whatever is wrong?
Tell me, did I mess up again?
You should do exactly as you please.
Seriously?
My King, why don't you tell me
what it is that you want me to do?
Um, master?
How do you suggest I handle this?
While we're at it, care to
explain why you're so far away?
Who do you think you are, huh?
What are you looking at, mister?
It's pretty obvious you just want
to get beat to death, don't you?
Underestimate us and we're
not gonna go easy on you!
Shall we try talking to
them to begin with? I see.
So even if we're up against that type,
we should learn about them first.
Makes sense. That's so you.
Your attention, young folks!
We're done with your
oppressive verbal attacks!
My name is Schwarz von Liechtenstein!
This is a riot and nothing more!
This is the Order of the King.
If you disperse now, all will be well.
Otherwise, you shall become
due on my sword and fall!
Who talks like that? Due on a sword?
Seriously?
Truly heinous!
Why not make it super easy and
say you're gonna beat us to death?
This is talking?
Well, think about it.
What purpose would it serve
being polite with criminals?
There's only two of you?
Whatcha gonna do?
We're never gonna disband
so you can forget that!
Spreading word of the hero and princess's
beauty throughout the
world is our sacred duty!
Huh?
That was the reason for rebellion?
We'll start with the royal capital!
Let's get em!
What should we do now, master? Do it.
Huh? Do it? Me?
Tell me, how long do you plan on
fearing the strength of that sword?
You shouldn't be allowing yourself to be
pushed around by power, you should use it!
Think back to your
training sessions with me.
Remember, Schwarz, and draw on the
strength from the past if that helps.
That sword of yours will cut through
whatever you want it to, isn't that right?
Don't forget it.
What are you nattering
on about, Pipsqueak?
Quit pretending you aren't
breaking out right now!
Our noble treasures!
Yes, I did it!
Did you see that, Master?
I did, I'm very confused.
THIS IS THE TRUE MIGHT
OF THE HOLY SWORD, Gram!
I'm so glad.
Gram, I'm just incredibly happy.
When you got eaten by that armor,
I thought that was the end for you.
Sorry? What's happening?
Why are we all standing out
in the field buck naked?
In front of the royal capital, too.
There's only men here.
Should we head home? Oh.
Yeah, since we have the opportunity
and all, let's head home naked!
Retreat!
Master we won right or
am I missing something
here huh shorts I think that sword may be
even more amazing than
we'd imagined please
praise me to master I beg
you if you'll excuse me
He complimented me, the king had
nothing but good things to say,
I was praised by the king, now that's
getting reincarnated in another world,
it really does feel like my reincarnation
is finally finally getting started,
man I'm so happy,
it's like spring has come, yes yes
very impressive you're amazing,
does this mean I'm actually
on the princess route,
should I just go ahead and save
this kingdom if you get too
cocky i will not hesitate to
punch you know that owie oh hey
it's Jinguuji Jinguuji listen
to this my reincarnation into
another world has finally gotten
started isn't that great really
i'm so happy for you uh huh
is it possible that Jinguuji
has been like this ever since
he separated from tachibana yes
there's really no point in playing
with him anymore fascinating
tachibana only cheated on Jinguuji
a little and he's like this
it seems Jinguuji was born of humans
after all cheated did you just say cheated
who cheated on whom tell
me everything because
i assure you you're
quite mistaken about my
relationship with
tachibana what
is this is he
human this is bad i'm
really feeling it in my legs
i've never seen them
move this way it's got
nothing to do with my
will they're moving with
incredible speed all on
their own this is surreal
my body's shaking so much
i have to apologize Guys,
I have to do it right
now, but I don't get it.
Did I say something wrong?
That's right, my name is Schwarz
von Liechtenstein-Lohengrum,
and I am a hero who will save
this world once and for all!
Except, is it right for a hero to
shrink back from an old guy in a suit?
It's begun, hasn't it?
My road to success.
I've seen it, I think.
The path to becoming a savior. You're...
you seem a little worried, Chinguchi.
Impossible!
He was confronted with
bloodlust and withstood it!
If you don't mind, I'll
listen to your worries.
My worries, huh?
But I don't have any worries.
Really?
But I thought you were pretty
concerned about Tachibana.
I'm sorry, but you were mistaken.
First of all, Tachibana went with
the princess willingly. I have no...
Listen, Jinguuji, feel free to
stop me if I'm wrong about this,
but aren't you just feeling depressed
after being left behind by Tachibana?
That's all, isn't it?
You don't know what you're talking about!
I'm doing great!
But you're literally deflated!
Anyway, if Tachibana wants to be
with the princess, that's that.
What's it to me?
Did you hear that personally or just
somewhere through the grapevine?
No, he definitely didn't ask directly.
Jinguji, could it be that you're just...
making your feelings of jealousy worse?
Are you trying to make me angry?
You're letting your bloodlust loose again!
If you think that'll make everything
go your way, you're wrong!
Why do you keep assuming I'm jealous?!
Oh
Let's go!
Fabulous!
Happiness!
Who are you?
Two are finally to.
It's been a while, everyone!
This is Schwarz von
Liechtenstein-Lohengramm.
Did you see what I just did?
I know I shouldn't say it
myself, but man, it's here!
The wind's really blowing my way!
Maybe a spin-off or something?
I'm sure an offer's coming,
and I'll be waiting for it.